What is diabetes? Have you ever
felt a black spot like a leaf in your face?
Hello friends, my name is Boxer
Chintan Liya. I would like to
give you some information about diabetes, which is called Madhumeha in Hindi, and its effects.
Today, more than 80 million people in India
suffer from diabetes, which is why
India has become the diabetic capital of the country.
Diabetes affects every part of the body
and affects your face.
Subscribe, we call it diabetes, through
which we can keep an eye on ourselves
and it can also come from inside. Ghee.
Subscribe, subscribe, subscribe. It is
more common in patients and
subscribe quickly. It is appointed in this thing,
so the patient thinks that everything is fine, so
he does not come to your doctor immediately after getting a prescription and
dies. He goes to your doctor
only for a checkup. In the last stage,
when there is swelling in the membrane or there is
bleeding,
then it becomes very late because every
diabetic patient should get his/her checkup done regularly so that if
anything related to diabetes is found,  If there are signs of retinopathy,
we will be able to treat it immediately. This is the need by
which we can save our eyesight and save ourselves
from the inside. Subscription to
this means that the school should subscribe, it is a
very important need
and if one tells about control in the morning by taking itself in the last three, then the
level of advancing should be less than 7. Along
with control, it is very important to control the blood pressure, one should
subscribe
and along with this, subscribe to food and drink, there should be
some physical activity,
your weight should be under control, subscribe should
stop smoking completely, so I hope
that my message reached you, if
you have any kind of ability, then please
contact me, if you
liked this video, then please
share it with your friends, my message can
reach even the elderly.